The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The sole reason you failed
was not because you were stopped
but because your master
the great Celestial General,
is unwilling
to be awakened.
Shut up !
Brother Xu...
Do it now
before it's too late !
Heavenly Chop !
Since he is unwilling,
stop clinging to your delusions.
My delusions ?
What do you know ?
My master's name is Gu Ziyuan,
a renowned Celestial King of the Thunder Celestial Realm.
And I
am his Sword Spirit,
the soul of the Ancient Abyss Sword.
In those years,
I followed him across the endless battlefields.
No matter where he pointed his sword,
no Celestials could resist him.
I thought this glory
would last forever.
That was until the day the Celestial Realm collapsed.
No !
That day,
I was one step too late.
Just one step...
How could he die ?
He can't die.
All I want...
All I want is for him to come back.
The Celestial Realm was destroyed
but it doesn't change anything for me.
To restore his scattered soul,
I used the sword as the foundation
and shaped this stone body for him.
To revive him,
I tried every surviving spell that was left behind.
After tens of thousands of years,
I finally found a spell.
But I can't leave this place.
So I had to wait.
A year,
100 years,
10 000 years,
but no one came here.
This used to be his cave.
The entire mountain is covered with the Annihilation Restrictions
that he placed himself.
Now,
will someone even recognize this restriction ?
At last, the heavens didn't forsake me.
30 000 years ago,
a member of the Li Family broke through the restrictions and entered.
I was finally able to plant the slave imprint
and leave this place.
My true body
must remain in the Thunder Celestial Realm
to protect my master's stone body from crumbling.
My body and soul were in two different places.
Every moment I existed within the Li Family
was like being sliced apart.
Only an Ascendant body
could host my soul.
The Li Family's bloodline was drained to nourish my soul,
weakening each generation even further.
So I fell into slumber
until
Li Jinglan reached Ascendant.
I refined a sword from the Li Family's bloodline.
My master's soul
was to finally be revived by it.
Everything was ready.
All that was missing
was blood of the same origin as my master.
I've taken advantage of the heavens,
the earth,
and the human heart.
It was supposed to be foolproof !
But in the end...
We pay respects to Master.
Ah Yuan...
Note: this is a nickname
Why...
Why did you give up !?
You told me
that we would travel to endless battlefields,
that we would tread across all 4 Celestial Realms.
You're not allowed to die !
Take the sword.
Wait for my return.
The Li Family's slave imprint
has not been destroyed.
A few years ago,
I awakened once more.
Was I wrong ?
The one controlling this body right now
is Li Yuan.
I...
was not wrong !
My master fought bloody wars for the Celestial Realm
to guard peace throughout the lands
while protecting the lives of countless Celestials.
He fought until his very last moment
until his body and his Dao were destroyed.
For what reason !?
I want to save him !
What's wrong with that !?
Since you refuse to help me,
I'll bury you here !
18th restriction,
Ten Thousand Plum Face the Origin !
18th restriction\N18 Plum Blossoms Restriction
You keep saying you want to revive him.
Your master fought to defend the Celestial Realm back then
but your obsession
sacrificed a number of innocent lives !
Is this really what he would have wanted ?
If he could see you now,
what would he think !?
You have no right to lecture me !
Heavenly Chop !
You dare !
My soul will never die !
No one can touch my master !
How do you know
what my sword is attacking ?
Stop !
No...
No !
If your heart is at peace,
will you dare to look up at him !?
Ah Yuan...
The sword body was destroyed.
He can't stay any longer.
I only wanted
the sword hilt
to no longer be empty...
You would stand on it forever,
while I stand on the sword tip
to help you battle the heavens and the earth.
Just like
it always was
in the past...
Feijing,
in the battle for the Celestial Realm,
I exhausted my strength and fell.
I had no regrets.
You trapped yourself for tens of thousands of years because of me,
overturning karma
and harming innocents.
It shouldn't have been this way.
But,
I'm sorry.
I ended up breaking my promise.
I'm dead,
my soul is dissipating.
Brother Xu,
thank you.
In that ancient battle,
countless Celestials died,
mountains and rivers were overturned.
No matter how deep the obsession,
no matter how brilliant the glory,
in the end
only these remnants remain.
A few days later
Celestial Valley ruins
This is a typical use of the fourth law of the 8 laws of celestial restrictions.
It should be the entrance of a celestial cave.
There must be treasures inside.
Brother Li !
Ninth Restriction,
Plum Dew Frost !
Ninth restriction\N18 Plum Blossoms Restriction
Brother Xu,
enter !
Fierce yet not evil...
This is no ordinary artifact.
Rise !
Go !
You used the 18 Plum Blossoms Restriction as a diversion,
that saved me some trouble.
Earlier, to resolve my family's crisis,
I lured you into the scheme without telling you the truth.
I feel
guilty about it.
This help
is just the beginning.
Once we leave the Thunder Celestial Realm,
if Brother Xu has the time,
please come to our ancestral inheritance temple.
My Li Family's Annihilation Restriction inheritance is special.
A jade slip
can't hold its full power.
Only by going in person to the ancestral inheritance temple
and receiving the Restriction Heart
can one obtain the complete inheritance.
Brother Xu,
I'm willing to give you half
of my Restriction Heart inheritance.
Brother Xu,
that place
should be the final secret cave of this fragment.
Ancient Celestial Residence
This armor's aura...
It's made of Ancient God skin !
An Ancient God's body is incredibly tough.
The Celestial Realm was actually able to peel off its skin
Ancient God Leather Armor
and tan it into an armor ?
It seems the former glory of the Celestial Realm
far exceeds what I had imagined.
Does Brother Xu recognize this thing ?
It reminds me of an old acquaintance.
I'll take the leather armor.
You can take
the bone finger.
What's this ?
What are those things ?
I have never heard of beings
this colossal.
Could these paintings
be a Celestial's imagination ?
8-star Ancient God...
The Celestial Realm and the Ancient God Clan
actually fought such a war.
27th Celestial Realm era, 16th year,
the Ancient Gods descended.
All Celestials joined the battle
and won.
All my artifacts were destroyed
so I fled here to refine and repair them.
In recognition of my military merit,
I was granted a piece of its hide
and tanned it into armor.
27th Celestial Realm era, 19th year,
a catastrophe !
The Celestial Emperor...
The Celestial Emperor went mad.
He pointed at the heavens and perished.
I saw it with my own eyes.
When the Celestial Emperor died,
I saw a sight
that shouldn't exist in this world.
Since I became a Celestial,
I was never afraid,
even against Ancient Gods.
But at that moment,
my soul felt as if it plunged into an icy abyss.
I was terrified.
As most of the Celestials fought to their death,
I had no choice but to escape.
A... A pair of eyes
kept following me.
I must
paint down
what I saw.
I must...
I must !
Back then,
what did he really see ?
What exactly caused the downfall
of the mighty Celestial Realm ?
These paintings
are extraordinary.
Brother Li must keep them hidden.
Don't show them to outsiders
or it will cause a disaster.
Don't worry, Brother Xu,
I understand the importance of this matter.
Brother Xu, what do you
plan to do next ?
I will find a quiet place
to cultivate in seclusion.
This slip has my unique communication restriction.
Brother Xu just needs to use his Divine Sense
and no matter how far apart we are,
you will sense my location.
If you ever need me in the future,
you can find me with it.
You contributed greatly
on our journey together.
Of these two items,
Brother Li can choose one first.
Brother Xu is generous.
I won't decline then.
This sword is quite helpful for my restrictions.
I'll take it.
Brother Xu,
until we meet again.
Take care.
Brother Xu is smart
and acts decisively.
In this opening of the Thunder Celestial Realm,
he is going to shake the world
and become famous.
Watch the second movie before episode 152. I will hold off on releasing episode 152 next week until the movie is out.\N\N“As most of the celestials battled, I escaped, and there was a pair of eyes following me… I had to paint what I saw…”\N\NThe handwriting became very sloppy at the end. It was easy to see how anxious the person writing this was.\N\N“I drew it… But what is this… What did I paint…” The note ended here.\N\NWang Lin’s eyes became serious. After pondering for a moment, he sat down before the table and picked up the brush. He wanted to feel exactly what happened when the celestial drew this.\N\NWang Lin held the brush and slowly closed his eyes. After a long time, he suddenly opened his eyes and his hand began writing according to the text. He gradually found a trace of what the celestial was feeling.\N\N“This celestial had just finished the painting, but he became even more confused. After leaving these words, there was a change. Someone must have arrived!” Wang Lin put down the brush and looked outside.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.